export const chapter11StudyData = [
  // Key Terms
  {
    id: "KT1101",
    front: "anal stage",
    back: "psychosexual stage in which children experience pleasure in their bowel and bladder movements"
  },
  {
    id: "KT1102",
    front: "analytical psychology",
    back: "Jung's theory focusing on the balance of opposing forces within one's personality and the significance of the collective unconscious"
  },
  {
    id: "KT1103",
    front: "archetype",
    back: "pattern that exists in our collective unconscious across cultures and societies"
  },
  {
    id: "KT1104",
    front: "collective unconscious",
    back: "common psychological tendencies that have been passed down from one generation to the next"
  },
  {
    id: "KT1105",
    front: "congruence",
    back: "state of being in which our thoughts about our real and ideal selves are very similar"
  },
  {
    id: "KT1106",
    front: "conscious",
    back: "mental activity (thoughts, feelings, and memories) that we can access at any time"
  },
  {
    id: "KT1107",
    front: "Contemporized-Themes Concerning Blacks Test (C-TCB)",
    back: "projective test designed to be culturally relevant to African Americans, using images that relate to African-American culture"
  },
  {
    id: "KT1108",
    front: "culture",
    back: "all of the beliefs, customs, art, and traditions of a particular society"
  },
  {
    id: "KT1109",
    front: "defense mechanism",
    back: "unconscious protective behaviors designed to reduce ego anxiety"
  },
  {
    id: "KT1110",
    front: "displacement",
    back: "ego defense mechanism in which a person transfers inappropriate urges or behaviors toward a more acceptable or less threatening target"
  },
  {
    id: "KT1111",
    front: "ego",
    back: "aspect of personality that represents the self, or the part of one's personality that is visible to others"
  },
  {
    id: "KT1112",
    front: "Five Factor Model",
    back: "theory that personality is composed of five factors or traits, including openness, conscientiousness, extroversion, agreeableness, and neuroticism"
  },
  {
    id: "KT1113",
    front: "genital stage",
    back: "psychosexual stage in which the focus is on mature sexual interests"
  },
  {
    id: "KT1114",
    front: "heritability",
    back: "proportion of difference among people that is attributed to genetics"
  },
  {
    id: "KT1115",
    front: "id",
    back: "aspect of personality that consists of our most primitive drives or urges, including impulses for hunger, thirst, and sex"
  },
  {
    id: "KT1116",
    front: "ideal self",
    back: "person we would like to be"
  },
  {
    id: "KT1117",
    front: "incongruence",
    back: "state of being in which there is a great discrepancy between our real and ideal selves"
  },
  {
    id: "KT1118",
    front: "individual psychology",
    back: "school of psychology proposed by Adler that focuses on our drive to compensate for feelings of inferiority"
  },
  {
    id: "KT1119",
    front: "inferiority complex",
    back: "refers to a person's feelings that they lack worth and don't measure up to others' or to society's standards"
  },
  {
    id: "KT1120",
    front: "latency period",
    back: "psychosexual stage in which sexual feelings are dormant"
  },
  {
    id: "KT1121",
    front: "locus of control",
    back: "beliefs about the power we have over our lives; an external locus of control is the belief that our outcomes are outside of our control; an internal locus of control is the belief that we control our own outcomes"
  },
  {
    id: "KT1122",
    front: "Minnesota Multiphasic Personality Inventory (MMPI)",
    back: "personality test composed of a series of true/false questions in order to establish a clinical profile of an individual"
  },
  {
    id: "KT1123",
    front: "neurosis",
    back: "tendency to experience negative emotions"
  },
  {
    id: "KT1124",
    front: "oral stage",
    back: "psychosexual stage in which an infant's pleasure is focused on the mouth"
  },
  {
    id: "KT1125",
    front: "personality",
    back: "long-standing traits and patterns that propel individuals to consistently think, feel, and behave in specific ways"
  },
  {
    id: "KT1126",
    front: "phallic stage",
    back: "psychosexual stage in which the focus is on the genitals"
  },
  {
    id: "KT1127",
    front: "projection",
    back: "ego defense mechanism in which a person confronted with anxiety disguises their unacceptable urges or behaviors by attributing them to other people"
  },
  {
    id: "KT1128",
    front: "Projective test",
    back: "personality assessment in which a person responds to ambiguous stimuli, revealing hidden feelings, impulses, and desires"
  },
  {
    id: "KT1129",
    front: "psychosexual stages of development",
    back: "stages of child development in which a child's pleasure-seeking urges are focused on specific areas of the body called erogenous zones"
  },
  {
    id: "KT1130",
    front: "rationalization",
    back: "ego defense mechanism in which a person confronted with anxiety makes excuses to justify behavior"
  },
  {
    id: "KT1131",
    front: "reaction formation",
    back: "ego defense mechanism in which a person confronted with anxiety swaps unacceptable urges or behaviors for their opposites"
  },
  {
    id: "KT1132",
    front: "real self",
    back: "person who we actually are"
  },
  {
    id: "KT1133",
    front: "reciprocal determinism",
    back: "belief that one's environment can determine behavior, but at the same time, people can influence the environment with both their thoughts and behaviors"
  },
  {
    id: "KT1134",
    front: "regression",
    back: "ego defense mechanism in which a person confronted with anxiety returns to a more immature behavioral state"
  },
  {
    id: "KT1135",
    front: "repression",
    back: "ego defense mechanism in which anxiety-related thoughts and memories are kept in the unconscious"
  },
  {
    id: "KT1136",
    front: "Rorschach Inkblot Test",
    back: "projective test that employs a series of symmetrical inkblot cards that are presented to a client by a psychologist in an effort to reveal the person's unconscious desires, fears, and struggles"
  },
  {
    id: "KT1137",
    front: "Rotter Incomplete Sentence Blank (RISB)",
    back: "projective test that is similar to a word association test in which a person completes sentences in order to reveal their unconscious desires, fears, and struggles"
  },
  {
    id: "KT1138",
    front: "selective migration",
    back: "concept that people choose to move to places that are compatible with their personalities and needs"
  },
  {
    id: "KT1139",
    front: "self-concept",
    back: "our thoughts and feelings about ourselves"
  },
  {
    id: "KT1140",
    front: "self-efficacy",
    back: "someone's level of confidence in their own abilities"
  },
  {
    id: "KT1141",
    front: "social-cognitive theory",
    back: "Bandura's theory of personality that emphasizes both cognition and learning as sources of individual differences in personality"
  },
  {
    id: "KT1142",
    front: "sublimation",
    back: "ego defense mechanism in which unacceptable urges are channeled into more appropriate activities"
  },
  {
    id: "KT1143",
    front: "superego",
    back: "aspect of the personality that serves as one's moral compass, or conscience"
  },
  {
    id: "KT1144",
    front: "TEMAS Multicultural Thematic Apperception Test",
    back: "projective test designed to be culturally relevant to minority groups, especially Hispanic youths, using images and storytelling that relate to minority culture"
  },
  {
    id: "KT1145",
    front: "temperament",
    back: "how a person reacts to the world, including their activity level, starting when they are very young"
  },
  {
    id: "KT1146",
    front: "Thematic Apperception Test (TAT)",
    back: "projective test in which people are presented with ambiguous images, and they then make up stories to go with the images in an effort to uncover their unconscious desires, fears, and struggles"
  },
  {
    id: "KT1147",
    front: "traits",
    back: "characteristic ways of behaving"
  },
  {
    id: "KT1148",
    front: "unconscious",
    back: "mental activity of which we are unaware and unable to access"
  },
  // Review Questions
  {
    id: "R1101",
    front: "Personality is thought to be ________.",
    back: "long term, stable and not easily changed"
  },
  {
    id: "R1102",
    front: "The long-standing traits and patterns that propel individuals to consistently think, feel, and behave in specific ways are known as ________.",
    back: "personality"
  },
  {
    id: "R1103",
    front: "________ is credited with the first comprehensive theory of personality.",
    back: "Freud"
  },
  {
    id: "R1104",
    front: "An early science that tried to correlate personality with measurements of parts of a person's skull is known as ________.",
    back: "phrenology"
  },
  {
    id: "R1105",
    front: "The id operates on the ________ principle.",
    back: "pleasure"
  },
  {
    id: "R1106",
    front: "The ego defense mechanism in which a person who is confronted with anxiety returns to a more immature behavioral stage is called ________.",
    back: "regression"
  },
  {
    id: "R1107",
    front: "The Oedipus complex occurs in the ________ stage of psychosexual development.",
    back: "phallic"
  },
  {
    id: "R1108",
    front: "The universal bank of ideas, images, and concepts that have been passed down through the generations from our ancestors refers to ________.",
    back: "collective unconscious"
  },
  {
    id: "R1109",
    front: "Self-regulation is also known as ________.",
    back: "will power"
  },
  {
    id: "R1110",
    front: "Your level of confidence in your own abilities is known as ________.",
    back: "self-efficacy"
  },
  {
    id: "R1111",
    front: "Jane believes that she got a bad grade on her psychology paper because her professor doesn't like her. Jane most likely has an _______ locus of control.",
    back: "external"
  },
  {
    id: "R1112",
    front: "Self-concept refers to ________.",
    back: "all of our thoughts and feelings about ourselves"
  },
  {
    id: "R1113",
    front: "The idea that people's ideas about themselves should match their actions is called ________.",
    back: "congruence"
  },
  {
    id: "R1114",
    front: "The way a person reacts to the world, starting when they are very young, including the person's activity level is known as ________.",
    back: "temperament"
  },
  {
    id: "R1115",
    front: "Brianna is 18 months old. She cries frequently, is hard to soothe, and wakes frequently during the night. According to Thomas and Chess, she would be considered ________.",
    back: "a difficult baby"
  },
  {
    id: "R1116",
    front: "According to the findings of the Minnesota Study of Twins Reared Apart, identical twins, whether raised together or apart have ________ personalities.",
    back: "very similar"
  },
  {
    id: "R1117",
    front: "Temperament refers to ________.",
    back: "inborn, genetically based personality differences"
  },
  {
    id: "R1118",
    front: "According to the Eysencks' theory, people who score high on neuroticism tend to be ________.",
    back: "anxious"
  },
  {
    id: "R1119",
    front: "The United States is considered a ________ culture.",
    back: "individualist"
  },
  {
    id: "R1120",
    front: "The concept that people choose to move to places that are compatible with their personalities and needs is known as ________.",
    back: "selective migration"
  },
  {
    id: "R1121",
    front: "Which of the following is NOT a projective test?",
    back: "Minnesota Multiphasic Personality Inventory (MMPI)"
  },
  {
    id: "R1122",
    front: "A personality assessment in which a person responds to ambiguous stimuli, revealing unconscious feelings, impulses, and desires ________.",
    back: "projective test"
  },
  {
    id: "R1123",
    front: "Which personality assessment employs a series of true/false questions?",
    back: "Minnesota Multiphasic Personality Inventory (MMPI)"
  }
];

export default chapter11StudyData;
